A Guide to the Margaret (Peggy) McGrath Rockefeller personal papers FA410
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2003:106 - Apartment Files, 3
  - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (MCHT), 1972-1984; 9
    - Acknowledgement Letters, 1980-1983; 3
      - Leede, Edward H., 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 26)
      - Lyman, Richard W., 1983 (Box 89, Folder 27)
      - M - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 28)
      - Neilson, Harry R. Jr., 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 29)
      - Nickerson, Albert and Liz, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 30)
      - Osborne, Frederic H. Jr., 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 31)
      - P - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 32)
      - Quesada, Elwood and Kate, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 33)
      - R - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 34)
      - S - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 35)
      - T - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 36)
      - W - General, 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 37)
      - Weaver, William B., 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 38)
      - Woodsum, Harold E. Jr., 1981-1983 (Box 89, Folder 39)
  - Environmental and Philanthropic Organizations, 1972-1985; 10
    - American Farmland Trust - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - American Farmland Trust - Meeting Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - American Farmland Trust - Meeting, Pocantico Hills, 1982 September 27-28 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - American Farmland Trust - Press Releases and Clippings, 1982-1983 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - American Farmland Trust - Reports and Research Materials, 1981-1984 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Conservation Clippings, 1973-1975 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Music Assistance Fund, 1972-1979 (Box 90, Folder 7, Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Nature Conservancy - Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Nature Conservancy - Handbooks and Programs, 1975-1977 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Nature Conservancy - Meeting Minutes, 1976-1979 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Trips, 1974-1981; 11
    - Australia - International Advisory Meetings, 1981 October 21 - November 8 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Brazil - Chase Board of Directors Meeting, 1980 October 7-14 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Cattle Buying Trips, 1979-1981 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Finland, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Galapagos Islands, 1980 December 24 - January 4 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Japan, Australia - Chase Manhattan Bank, 1978 November (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Japan, Australia, Brazil, 1979 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - London - Trilateral Meetings, 1980 March 22-27 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Norway, London, 1981 June 18-29 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Accession 2005:030, 1978-1990; 4; 0.44 Cubic Feet 1 standard document storage box
  - Letters of Sympathy Death of her father, F. Sims McGrath, 1959 September 13 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Letters of Sympathy Death of her mother, Neva Van Smith McGrath, 1963 August (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Letters to and from F. Sims McGrath, 1926-1960 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Estate of Neva Van Smith McGrath, Personal Letters, 1949-1965 (Box 93, Folder 4)